Me.
Me. Me. Me. Me.
Me
me. Me
.
But the.
Problem go. A.
Long Long Long Long Long. Long long.
Long. Long.
Long. Long long. Long.
Long long.
Long
long. Long
.
Rick wants to hire me he said
a new studio. Where. India
. When
I don't remember what the
how do you know there's
a year for that I think they say the
fourteenth century but the fourteenth century
was recently you know but I don't know if
that's when the moguls are truly involved
was in India eleven
definitely B.C. It is B.C.
For sure and I think it's I you know there
I don't. Know that because he raised
that temple they said that John was born
there and I don't believe but that's what
they say. Is in the state of the British
It's right there therefore the story has
to be true it's really based on as real
as event as the Bible is based on if you
want to know the whole story.
Because father had always three
wives three wives four sons four sons three
right OK I know the name of the sons by
the way you know that was
a way for us what it meant so. And. And
our son was wrong so it's our son
was one. Case and was so impressed
and shot through and I think was the brother
which means you had to be. So with us
and see that was Rahm's wife right and see
that I know also came she does father
would. See those many names only be
wonderful. Thank you Johnny Also joining me
also representing the R.N.
By his device. I saw unveiling where the
where the where the he I saw play called
Where the Right which I learned was
another name was either Ramos about to be
crowned by the shirt as the king and.
Went to him and because she had got this
doesn't really I think she'd taken care of
him when he was really sick or something
like that Yes And and so at that point he
said to her that you have one boring day
you ask of me I will do and so she went
and asked him to send drum away fourteen
years thinking there was
a long enough time that if you go away for
fourteen years you're pretty much out of
sight out of mind.
My son today I wish to crown
you. But my evil scheming wife.
Just reminded me of an ancient.
One of this fall instead of. I
must banish you to the forest for
fourteen years. Good bye boy
you are noble and good the
embodiment of righteousness
a brave warrior princess joy of
heaven and. The ideal man made the
gods. Don't let the door hit your ass on
the way out that's what she asked for and
the shot was heartbroken. But. You don't
think that given that all Indian men are
true to their word. He has to he
had to do that and then he'd.
Indeed die no I don't think what he does
he died eventually Yeah but all those all
those but. Only it ironically
laws I've seen when I was
a kid. There's big scene of a
drama dramatic he's having
a heart attack when his son is going away
I says Assuming I don't think he's unwell
I do things only happens when he goes
yeah that's true and he also has
a huge issue right is the gravity of my
guild has drawn bright sun and wrong and it
was told to go away as he said he would he
didn't create any problems you're going
to see why he's going to said if that is
your wish father I should go you know and
he went and he does it if you go I
go No see the forest is be sacked
by rocks. They hired
a wise man and it gets their
picture by us I must fight them
alone but damn A woman's place is
next to it has been I really accept
any hardship I cannot live without you I
cannot live without you I cannot leave.
Now.
We have.
Yeah.
You know. Not.
That.
On this you it's only
a six contract I'll be
back before you know. When
I was the evil king of Lanka and he
just still. We were incredibly learned
meant what I understand Robin it was
actually the only bad thing he seems to
have done the sketches he thought I could
not see them which is kind of interesting
because. Like everything else about him
seems to be like he's this really learned
guy he's knows all these weapons he plays
to the right gods I guess so all the stuff
he's like this good king. Except that
over time we've been led to believe more
and more that he's this complete gamble on
the ceiling that's really been an island
all children Island Yeah you know he was
a devoted she was yeah. And he plays
well this is true meaning of it is
interesting I think for say What is
interesting yeah that's also I don't know
there's yeah there's there's this
whole thing about how devoted
a fan I was and he's asking.
For some wish and you
know he is basically playing because in
the States so. In my in my doctor felt
better because this
point what it's been to
a man right now at least let me know that
this is new Nothing much what I'm really
impressed as you know that he was
a king of. Huge. But some people I
was alone it's the same country I
think well the point is that's
where we think they build a bridge
a bridge just still exists so NASA images
see really yeah so that's also the
startling thing must be true
then. It's really sort of
a when the moon. Is in the. Right so.
I'm missing
a pun named God that would be awful but
that was the one of the super macabre she
was Robin
a sister novena drama slaughter bureaucracies
in the forest you must take revenge
on board must. His power for you ceased to
narc bother me with your petty
cunts. Do you brother. Have you
seen TO SEE THEM TO she is the
most beautiful woman or her.
Has this bed like that.
But I notice it's her
hands their legs. Notices
her breasts like big noun
bottom juicy.
Makes your wife Robin steal her
from Adama do or do it must.
You must help me I want
wrongs for yourself into
a. Promise. Guard
a. Good in that house. Will you be mine
ah was.
What is. Holding do you.
Want your captured for me
I don't know. Oh no please.
You ask Was saw
a little and give me so much but promise
you won't leave the hot while I'm gone or
just as dangerous I
promise. I love you. You
see.
And do me now it come and
only now I've had then my.
Then bid game do me. The gay why don't we.
I now I knew how good it
was to. Do one who know
what to be. And why down
deep in it I. Have been out. And what
I need to get out and they take.
Me to eat what wouldn't I do
a lot of that matter and.
Bang and rot beyond me
they would all hit the ball oh yeah yeah.
Through Tim and down. Broadwood and I do.
Mean. Live it. It On. All the.
Rides and with.
Him. Making.
Good money.
On the. Making board mom.
Do. Good when.
Thing out.
But you don't see that does that how she
actually is able to tell these people
wishing she drops her jewelry along the way
right and that's how they were able to
find that it went all the way up to.
My stitching job exactly so she had
a ring
a drug dealer in the course. I mean no she
demanded she's not wearing any jewelry
because she left everything
before she left you
a day and she came back she left everything
yesterday she just came in her Sunday I
think loads don't challenge
these stories. She's gone
I told her not to leave the heart
or how would I ever find her. Feet.
First into what has become.
Actually the origins of
a new man. All these demons were attacking
the earth and supposedly all the God
they were in went to Vishnu and said that
please help us please help us to Vishnu
said that he was going to be born on earth
as wrong but he would want to push north
or that he can sing the best thus of dark
then incarnate and so the didn't want to
put the last one not coming as it was.
So anyway he said that what we'll do is.
We'll be born. As someone who
gets me to Shiva was actually
a new one as incarnation of order not that
I didn't know that here and. So who are
actually born with the sole purpose or
eventually meeting up with the wrong heading
in the gutter was the
reason for it but. Any.
Of. Our when you. Who are
you I am all along the
monkey already on Song of the when.
I am around dreams or value of you
let us be I'll. Be Yours
seven whatever. Now go find.
Hello It's Me Dave where are you
here Fandor I'm silly at home
you have a home phone of
course you've been gone
a month and you never even told me your
phone number I didn't well I have some good
news they've extended my contract another
year what another year you said you'd be
back in six months but I like it
here what about me what about Lexi.
What about our apartment.
What about I was.
Don't cry. For. You I Love.
Be you could come here. She
says under tree and she weeps
and and the things over on the. Priest her
mom and all the evil people and you know
all these movies and all these shores we've
seen and all these evil people come and
sort of scare her and she plays to it but
I think the thing is that but nobody
thing is and those are the women whatever
the women demon whatever was going to
protect amazed by her devotion if you will
into Dom and said I'm going to comes and
says What can brown do for you blah blah
blah that I can't that I can but she still
Dromgoole coming and you still have one
last chance because once he comes here you
know your ass is grass.
I love you see you must
be my wife now I level only Velma.
I am the chaste and virtuous wife of
another man. I belong to them all
as the rays belong to the sun.
Give me back to Rama all use and
soon he had his mighty bow that
resound like in the tumbler.
Dunmore a man speaks sweet deed to
a woman now more she inserted Sarah.
You'll have to months to decide
lady then and you shall shed in
my hand if you do not Matty me
my. DOCTOR to you'll fall
out of my breakfast.
Your ugly yellow eyes should fall out of
your head as you stare at me so lust for
lead other not the only reason I do not
reduce you to that is with my own blazing
pollen is because Romney has
not ordered me to do so.
All.
Has to.
Play one.
Song.
Goes.
And.
That. She also made
a one shooter mistakes in fact you're just
gone back on him on the idea of my match
my manage to come to see it means that
you're one of the I think jump on the
monkeys back go back chill out hundreds
would be fine OK this is it possible she
didn't trust the monkey or together it is
possible it is possible that you don't
trust the monkey I think she absolutely
trusted the monkey as she wanted him at
like she wanted him and because that's
what it's like you got to prove it to me
baby but not only that it's. Like you know
but she also wanted the evil king to be
defeated I think that was the thing that
my husband should come and actually do
just that and that's why don't you
go back so that even doesn't have
a hostage and then do it but it was almost
like she's trying to glue to fight on
through this whole process scene or like
like my man will come and he's he's
capable of this and he's. Been to
a lot. Well
this is what the monkeys because they
actually they were flying monkeys there. What
I understand is different from monkeys right
I mean they're like what I understand
when I was young there were monkeys were
one kind of one species and then the
liner's were actually another
species of a half man half
a monkey OK because they had bales and
all but that they're not like yeah yeah
everything that tail and they were half
they had every half monkey in or more yeah
that's what the Army was because otherwise
they were these these two brothers they
didn't have any are two brothers and then
all of Supremes and big army all the
right along the line are saying of honest
you know I'm right. On assemble the
monkey warriors reach out across the sea
to long and rescue feet off yes my lawn
we march AK wants. Since.
I just had
a. Small. Good what's
going on happen to me.
Now there comes
a. Knock on my. Goodness
gracious can it be the most
common bag. Nothin at.
All. If. Not.
I know it is an ailment of him and I.
Must leave it there.
Sounds like. I don't.
Know. Because if the brothers
would visit that they didn't even know good
mother has been mugged if they keep it
out of the difficult that's
a good beginning about the fact. That the
mother nothing mother did they could be
the best that they.
Were in India no kissing.
Let me take your back.
Here you are. Right.
Little I know what he did what he did when
he was so hard and. Hug her and kiss her
no I don't think so she was
very. Cool because he thought.
This point what he is going to get up.
You have lived in another man's house so
you are unfit to be in my life. I have
done my duty in rescuing you from the enemy
and of ending the insults to myself I
have suspicions about your
character and conduct
a domino was aware of your beauty he cannot
have kept you in his house for so long
without touching you the very sight of you
in forty you are free to go wherever you
want I have no more use for you thought
if I had known this I would have
killed myself before instead
you this was build me
a funeral pyre I cannot bear to live despite
my virtues my husband has rejected me
he's obviously doubting her. Of pure ness
I find the whole pureness think really
hard I find it really weird that nobody is
commenting at all one for not forcibly I
know I know we should come know what somebody
you know yet what would be the appeal
but in terms of villains right I mean we
expect millions to be villainous Yes this
is
a guy that's like if you don't come to me
willingly. I would not that you are right
I would not force you my house I would not
force myself on you but you never had
sex with no as I as I see
the poor hour ago by
a five child of five. To
me.
You
you are
.
Radio. Down let me know Babylon.
Finding.
To. Do.
Down there was. At home. Mom
down. On.
A.
Monday. Ron Paul you.
Know. That. And he's still
not convinced seemed like
after she went through the trial by fire
I mean it's almost like no I thought he
was convinced he didn't it
was Bill pressure later with
a wash because of Washington yet because
he was convinced it was like he doubted it
was OK you all feel as he did hug and
then flawless one from the heavens or
something. Webs I guess you have
you're after all are you forgive me.
If. I leave only for you.
OK they want me to attend this meeting so
much they're going to fly me all the way
to New York five days all expenses paid
debts parades it'll be fun for you.
See you next week.
No no no the flying
chariots on the God sent
a chariot I don't know something about for
I'm jumping straight I finally I'm fine
I found it to be totally cool with the
world's first airplane or something like the
first it actually flew about
I was on the on a board when
a bird. I think was actually a
flying machine in the coppered like
a log none was like an elaborate structure
and that's what he came back on the
flinch I spoke of him and him that was one
of the in the jumbo jets all those and
maybe
a silent movie but I was yeah but that's
what I mean it was like this thing he was
in the bottom in line now. I guess what
is happening the fourteen years we're
finishing off so they had to find
a quick way to get back. How
.
Then.
Again if you. Lie.
You.
Have.
This.
Code was doing. Last minute like to.
Thank.
You. IT'S IT'S IT'S
IT'S IT'S IT'S pretty cool.
That the fans.
I.
Was.
Pregnant that's one before.
He joined the mile high club.
We don't know exactly where she got
very soon thereafter which is why it's
conceivable that some of that argued the
love that that she wasn't pregnant because
of Rob but I think it was blasphemy it is.
I'm not like. The woman who was left in a
lot of men's. Room but that happens with
a dog and that can be said it will be the
IT WILL BE story but it will be the way
the long. One the Toby's wife wife is with
somebody else really she comes back and
goes where you think I'm wrong I'm like
mama to take somebody's back right now so
obviously you know the movie is there in
the washroom and I watched and then you
have
a lot of. Rum says I can I go drool in my
subjects don't respect me tonight and so
you have to actually that's anybody's
story that's really been answered.
Would you like to take
a trip but we just got here
yeah I get it packing brother
Luxman my wife's dubious reputation cast
doubt upon my own you must drive Seattle
to the forest and abandon her I cannot have
her in my kingdom. I think basically as
a king he had to sort of do if the common
man was doing that to their wives and why
would the King treat his wife any
differently because it was like
a letter going on because he thought he
was impure but because he said that to be
a king is the respect of his subjects right
and he can be considered but I don't
think you know the guy should ensure that
he always had this element of doubt I
mean it coupled with of course you know his
says virtually that everybody spoke off
and you know that he kept his word to his
dad and then his his subjects' is his
kingdom but I felt like you always had
this doubt that she might not be pure.
And. Neat.
You. Know.
Please. God.
I must have committed that doubt of us
in the previous life to deserve such
suffering would I not caring. I
would throw myself into the liver
she's always shown to be pregnant in after
Adam after she's banished and she's
gone into the forest again and you know
there she meets that teacher. Sorry So
that's how I'll make it out of the mine up
because she thought all the story to em
.
Was.
I learned but.
Yeah.
Well born to sit on the forest and actually
taught by one the king who taught them
how to sing all the songs
praising their own.
Neck the singing the praises of
it all. That was during the rally
love the love does
a lot of drama drama has just struck our
lives that come out is our guiding light
the things that. Our hearts not
that I find our way of life
our weak place love not in. Touch.
The touch. Of.
Love the way our mothers. Are just
what drama sure Valmeyer just
dramatize that Rahmat is our
guiding light. That love that
sound odd that I am relieved by our way of
life we have loved our week days out of
nothing in this hour.
Please take me back to you.
All the way any thing.
If you had
a girlfriend who was being treated really
badly by like her ex or by her current
boyfriend what oh and and she kept saying
No Every day I'm going to make sure I
cook for him and send him
a hot lunch at noon I'm going to listen
he doesn't like you and talk to you You
gotta move on something's wrong OK he
doesn't this put every day I mean I feel
I feel. It was it was the whole good good
and bad thing that we always want people
to be it all good or bad I think she also
has grown issues like she did go back
with one once you have saved hundreds
and thousands of people forming killed
monkeys specially young whatever animal
rights and and then she she prayed for his
diary to come on but also at that point of
time it was just that unconditional love
you know for her she was like OK I think
and I think this is this is the part of
the female perspective I disagree with
because it's like then we can say Oh yeah
because she loved him so she did it you
know it's like you know what you should
love someone who doesn't interest you so
badly OK that's her mistake that's hence
unconditional love.
Well. You.
That.
And when Ron was in the forest and could
these two boys singing he didn't know
where they were when he came up and he
was just like Who are they while you and
that's when he finds out that. C.
Does the end of the his children
my son. Off to don't do I owe you
a palace to rule with me forty Don't you.
But then he wants to go and push back
but he still has
a number to. Sit up with yes
of course see that. All it
has to do is prove her purity again another
trial by fire perhaps already could
drive trial by water you know see if she
sinks or floats if she thinks she's
feeling if she floats know it if she
floats she's yours if he also to
prove the purity one more time I think
I sure don't know what they are so or
whatever she says I shall prove my purity
to you. If I have always been told to
mama if I have never heard of another man
I am completely floored in body and soul
. Dick leave bad.
For.
Since. You.
Made. On five.
Dollars Dollars on nobody else thought.
Of you caught my. Bargain.
On Dr Drew. I use the. Thing all the tax.
Man. Now he. Says that
Paul. Paul Ron. Paul Paul and Paul
Nobody has you.
Hold.
Off. On the last. Thing
I'm
a been. Taken
Away don't know if. But.
But I.
Can't.
Thank you.
Long. Long long. Long long long.
Long long. Long.
Long Long Long Long Long
Long. Long long long.
Long
long long
.
Off.
Going.
On. Off. Off.
The.